They don't want you to believe what she saw.
The Woman in Cabin 10 is a mystery, thriller,
crime film directed by Simon Stone.
On a lavish yacht for an assignment, a journalist sees a passenger go overboard.
But when no one believes her, she risks her life to uncover the truth.
Laura 'Lo' Blacklock, played by Keira Knightley.
Richard Bullmer, played by Guy Pearce.
Ben Morgan, played by David Ajala.
Carrie, played by Gitte Witt.
Dr. Robert Mehta, played by Art Malik.
Rowan, played by Gugu Mbatha-Raw.
The Woman in Cabin 10 is a 2025 psychological thriller film directed by Simon Stone, who co-wrote the
screenplay with Joe Shrapnel and Anna Waterhouse, based on the 2016 novel by Ruth Ware.
The film stars Keira Knightley, Guy Pearce, Art Malik, Gugu
Mbatha-Raw, Kaya Scodelario, Daniel Ings and Hannah Waddingham.
Netflix released The Woman in Cabin 10 on October 10, 2025 to
mostly middling and poor responses from critics.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
boat, investigation, fake identity, murder.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.